<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/chen/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/chen/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-02-13T21:53:22+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/chen/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Chen Zhu</title><subtitle>Un-Teaching and Intellectual Un-Property</subtitle><entry><title type="html">How to turn Legacy PPTX files to Org-Mode</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/chen/2020/10/06/legacy_pptx_to_org/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to turn Legacy PPTX files to Org-Mode" /><published>2020-10-06T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-10-06T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/chen/2020/10/06/legacy_pptx_to_org</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/chen/2020/10/06/legacy_pptx_to_org/">&lt;p&gt;As I no longer use MS powerpoint for making presentation slides, I need to convert all my old pptx files into the &lt;code&gt;org&lt;/code&gt; format.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Pandoc&lt;/code&gt;, at the moment, does not seem to support &lt;code&gt;pptx&lt;/code&gt; as an input format. So I have to find a workaround. Here is a 3-step solution that seems to work well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Step (i): Use LibreOffice Impress to open an pptx files&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Step (ii): Export pptx file to as a single html file (and name it as &lt;code&gt;legacy.html&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://filedn.com/lvjEGnSit1pQw941XB4wFTk/blog-image/ppt2org/pptx2-single-html.png&quot; alt=&quot;https://filedn.com/lvjEGnSit1pQw941XB4wFTk/blog-image/ppt2org/pptx2-single-html.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Step (iii):  Pandoc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, &lt;code&gt;pandoc legacy.html -o emacs-org.org&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That's it!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Chen Zhu</name></author><summary type="html">As I no longer use MS powerpoint for making presentation slides, I need to convert all my old pptx files into the org format. Pandoc, at the moment, does not seem to support pptx as an input format. So I have to find a workaround. Here is a 3-step solution that seems to work well. Step (i): Use LibreOffice Impress to open an pptx files Step (ii): Export pptx file to as a single html file (and name it as legacy.html) Step (iii): Pandoc Finally, pandoc legacy.html -o emacs-org.org That's it!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">To Deft Or Notdeft</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/chen/2020/09/20/To-Deft-or-NotDeft/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="To Deft Or Notdeft" /><published>2020-09-20T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-09-20T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/chen/2020/09/20/To-Deft-or-NotDeft</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/chen/2020/09/20/To-Deft-or-NotDeft/">&lt;h1&gt;Deft, NotDeft and Xapian&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The number of my org notes in my &lt;code&gt;deft&lt;/code&gt; directories has just gone beyond 600. To search from the official &lt;code&gt;deft&lt;/code&gt; interface becomes a bit clunky and unwieldy. So I finally decide to install the &lt;code&gt;NotDeft&lt;/code&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://tero.hasu.is/notdeft/&quot;&gt;package&lt;/a&gt; that employs the external search engine &amp;#8220;Xapian&amp;#8221;. One of the biggest advantages with &lt;code&gt;NotDeft&lt;/code&gt; is that you can have more granular search results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For note-taking, I become attached to &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/org-roam/org-roam&quot;&gt;Org-Roam&lt;/a&gt;, which makes bi-directional linking incredibly easy and smooth. However, a normal Org-Roam query does not do a full-text search. That's why &lt;code&gt;NotDeft&lt;/code&gt; (with Xapian) is still relevant. &lt;code&gt;NotDeft&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;Org-Roam&lt;/code&gt; complement, rather than compete against, each other. The two packages work together to build a desktop wiki system for my purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;CJK search&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Notdeft's Xapian does not search for Chinese characters by default. You need to enable xapian to search for CJK characters (see an Emacs-China &lt;a href=&quot;https://emacs-china.org/t/notdeft/11314/8&quot;&gt;discussion here&lt;/a&gt;). Just add the follow elisp code to your emacs config file will do the trick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;setenv&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;XAPIAN_CJK_NGRAM&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;1&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Display markdown files in NotDeft&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also need to enable a few secondary extensions (such as markdown files) to be &amp;#8220;seen&amp;#8221; by NotDeft. This is achieved through adding &lt;code&gt;(setq notdeft-secondary-extensions &amp;#39;(&amp;quot;md&amp;quot; &amp;quot;markdown&amp;quot;))&lt;/code&gt; to my emacs config file.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;p.s.&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deft is an emulation of &lt;a href=&quot;https://notational.net/&quot;&gt;Notational Velocity&lt;/a&gt;, which is said to be “modeless” and “mouseless” with the ability to do incremental searching.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Chen Zhu</name></author><category term="note-taking" /><summary type="html">Deft, NotDeft and Xapian The number of my org notes in my deft directories has just gone beyond 600. To search from the official deft interface becomes a bit clunky and unwieldy. So I finally decide to install the NotDeft package that employs the external search engine &amp;#8220;Xapian&amp;#8221;. One of the biggest advantages with NotDeft is that you can have more granular search results. For note-taking, I become attached to Org-Roam, which makes bi-directional linking incredibly easy and smooth. However, a normal Org-Roam query does not do a full-text search. That's why NotDeft (with Xapian) is still relevant. NotDeft and Org-Roam complement, rather than compete against, each other. The two packages work together to build a desktop wiki system for my purpose. CJK search Notdeft's Xapian does not search for Chinese characters by default. You need to enable xapian to search for CJK characters (see an Emacs-China discussion here). Just add the follow elisp code to your emacs config file will do the trick. (setenv &amp;quot;XAPIAN_CJK_NGRAM&amp;quot; &amp;quot;1&amp;quot;) Display markdown files in NotDeft I also need to enable a few secondary extensions (such as markdown files) to be &amp;#8220;seen&amp;#8221; by NotDeft. This is achieved through adding (setq notdeft-secondary-extensions &amp;#39;(&amp;quot;md&amp;quot; &amp;quot;markdown&amp;quot;)) to my emacs config file. p.s. Deft is an emulation of Notational Velocity, which is said to be “modeless” and “mouseless” with the ability to do incremental searching.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Temple OS</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/chen/2020/06/10/templeOS/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Temple OS" /><published>2020-06-10T18:56:12+01:00</published><updated>2020-06-10T18:56:12+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/chen/2020/06/10/templeOS</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/chen/2020/06/10/templeOS/">&lt;p&gt;Is Terry Davis’s TempleOS the software equivalent of Beethoven’s Symphony No.5?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Terry_A._Davis&quot;&gt;Davis (1969–2018)&lt;/a&gt; is a solitary programmer who authors this public-domain operating system called &lt;a href=&quot;https://templeos.org/&quot;&gt;TempleOS&lt;/a&gt; written in the programming language called HolyC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also happen to notice that Davis was born in the same year as Linus Torvalds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/icaruszhu/learning/master/image/blog-image/TempleOS-download-screenshot.png&quot; alt=&quot;templeOS&quot; width=&quot;95%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Chen Zhu</name></author><summary type="html">Is Terry Davis’s TempleOS the software equivalent of Beethoven’s Symphony No.5?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Linux Distro Hopping</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/chen/2020/05/31/distro-hopping/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Linux Distro Hopping" /><published>2020-05-31T15:49:54+01:00</published><updated>2020-05-31T15:49:54+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/chen/2020/05/31/distro-hopping</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/chen/2020/05/31/distro-hopping/">&lt;p&gt;I have tried numerous Linux distros (including Fedora, OpenSuse, MX Linux, ElementaryOS, Ubunutu (with Gnome and Mate), Mint, Manjaro, KDE Neon, Puppy Linux, TinyCore, etc etc) in the past. So I think I am a qualified “Linux distro hopper”. I have not tried FreeBSD, simply because BSD is seriously NOT a Linux distribution ;-)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The current GNU/Linux system I settle on is Kubuntu 20.04 (a Ubunutu distribution with the K Desktop Environment). I like the KDE Plasma experience a lot. Almost one month ago (April 2020), I tried to upgrade from Ubuntu 18.04 to Ubuntu 20.04, but failed spectacularly. This failure made me look around for something else and I chanced upon Manjaro KDE (which is an ARCH based distribution). I used Manjaro KDE for about a month and I liked it a lot. &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Pacman&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Yay&lt;/code&gt; made it super easy to install bleeding-edge software packages from &lt;a href=&quot;https://aur.archlinux.org/&quot;&gt;AUR or ARCH User Repository&lt;/a&gt;. For example, it is a bit a pain to install the latest version of &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;pandoc&lt;/code&gt; from the official Ubuntu software repo. With &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;pacman&lt;/code&gt;, all I need to do is to type a one-line command &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;pacman -S pandoc&lt;/code&gt; in the terminal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Manjaro KDE, for some unknown reason, was not able to power on the two external moniters connected to my laptop. (I suffer from screen fatigue after spending long hours working in front of my laptop. That’s why I need extra screens to make my eyes feel a bit more comfortable) This became a major reason why I needed another distro and I eventually ended up, thankfully, with the current Kubuntu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish, and I only wish, I will not “hop” around in the next five or even ten years (but who knows!). There has been both euphoria and frustration in distro hopping, indeed!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Chen Zhu</name></author><summary type="html">I have tried numerous Linux distros (including Fedora, OpenSuse, MX Linux, ElementaryOS, Ubunutu (with Gnome and Mate), Mint, Manjaro, KDE Neon, Puppy Linux, TinyCore, etc etc) in the past. So I think I am a qualified “Linux distro hopper”. I have not tried FreeBSD, simply because BSD is seriously NOT a Linux distribution ;-)</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Adopt easy-jekyll for emacs</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/chen/2020/05/30/using-easy-jekyll/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Adopt easy-jekyll for emacs" /><published>2020-05-30T23:03:07+01:00</published><updated>2020-05-30T23:03:07+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/chen/2020/05/30/using-easy-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/chen/2020/05/30/using-easy-jekyll/">&lt;p&gt;I have now managed to integrate Jekyll blogging into my Emacs workflow. I am so glad to find the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;easy-jekyll&lt;/code&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/masasam/emacs-easy-jekyll&quot;&gt;package&lt;/a&gt;, which can be installed from &lt;a href=&quot;https://melpa.org/#/easy-jekyll&quot;&gt;Melpa&lt;/a&gt;. One can also install it with the good old &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jwiegley/use-package&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;use-package&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in your emacs init file. The official package recommends the following code for installation:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-lisp highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;use-package&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;easy-jekyll&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:init&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;setq&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;easy-jekyll-basedir&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;~/my-awesome-site/&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;setq&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;easy-jekyll-url&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;https://yourblogdomain&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;setq&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;easy-jekyll-sshdomain&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;blogdomain&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;setq&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;easy-jekyll-root&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;/home/blog/&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;setq&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;easy-jekyll-previewtime&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;300&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;ss&quot;&gt;:bind&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;C-c C-e&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;easy-jekyll&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;))&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the link to &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;easy-jekyll&lt;/code&gt; on Github:
https://github.com/masasam/emacs-easy-jekyll (licensed under GPLv3)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once installed, the eponymous &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;easy-jekyll&lt;/code&gt; command is recommeded to be bound to &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;C-c C-e&lt;/code&gt; (see above). However, I find this keybinding clashes with &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;org-export-dispatch&lt;/code&gt; if you are already working in an org file. So better avoid using &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;C-c C-e&lt;/code&gt; here and choose a non-clashing keybinding, which can be easily done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following the instruction, I also need to write a simple  &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;delopy.sh&lt;/code&gt; bash script stored in my jekyll root directory. This allows me to automatically &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;push&lt;/code&gt; (aka “upload”) the updated blog article(s) to my github pages by pressing &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;G&lt;/code&gt; on the keyboard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once everything is (minimally) configured , &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;easy-jekyll&lt;/code&gt; is truly EASY to use!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PS: I also learn that it is possible to write Jekyll blogs with Emacs’s super powerful &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Org&lt;/code&gt; mode. There seem to be many ways of doing this. Elsa Gonsiorowski has done a fantastic survey on different ways of implementing an Org-led workflow. https://www.gonsie.com/blorg/survey-org-jekyll.html&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Chen Zhu</name></author><summary type="html">I have now managed to integrate Jekyll blogging into my Emacs workflow. I am so glad to find the easy-jekyll package, which can be installed from Melpa. One can also install it with the good old use-package in your emacs init file. The official package recommends the following code for installation:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Sumptuary Law and Ambush Marketing</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/chen/publication/2020/03/22/sumptuary-law/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sumptuary Law and Ambush Marketing" /><published>2020-03-22T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-03-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/chen/publication/2020/03/22/sumptuary-law</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/chen/publication/2020/03/22/sumptuary-law/">&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;my-article-adjudicating-sartorial-elegance&quot;&gt;My Article: Adjudicating Sartorial Elegance&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;full-title&quot;&gt;Full title&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Adjudicating Sartorial Elegance from the Court”: My new article on the sumptuary impulse of  anti-ambush marketing law in the latest issue of QMJIP&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;abstract&quot;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ambush marketing, sometimes also known as guerrilla marketing, comprises attempts to create an unauthorized association with mega-sporting  events (such as the Olympic Games and the FIFA World Cup) without  obtaining official sponsorship agreements. This article contends that  the contemporary law of sports sponsorships against ambush marketing  harbours a palpable but much-neglected sumptuary impulse, which has  never before been adequately scrutinized. It shows that pre-modern  sumptuary law strangely resonates with modern anti-ambush law’s  sumptuary obsession with the visual order of symbols and images as  prestige signifiers. It also reveals an ongoing ‘intellectual property’  turn in the recent development of sumptuary anti-ambush law-making,  whose ambition is to reify sports-derived sumptuary distinction into a  thing-in-itself for nearly absolute ‘property’ protection. My argument  is illustrated by a carefully selected number of ambush disputes  including &lt;em&gt;Australian Olympic Committee (AOC) v Telstra&lt;/em&gt;, which represents the latest development in this field of law.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;full-text-download&quot;&gt;Full text download&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elgaronline.com/view/journals/qmjip/10-1/qmjip.2020.01.03.xml?&amp;amp;pdfVersion=true&quot;&gt;free for download from here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;citation&quot;&gt;Citation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chen Wei Zhu, “Adjudicating Sartorial Elegance from the Court—The Sumptuary  Impulse in the Law of Modern Sports Sponsorship against Ambush  Marketing”, &lt;em&gt;Queen Mary Journal of Intellectual Property&lt;/em&gt; (2020)10 (1) 62–86&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Chen Zhu</name></author><category term="publication" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">IP Teaching in the new semester</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/chen/teaching/2020/01/16/IP-teaching/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="IP Teaching in the new semester" /><published>2020-01-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-01-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/chen/teaching/2020/01/16/IP-teaching</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/chen/teaching/2020/01/16/IP-teaching/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://filedn.com/lvjEGnSit1pQw941XB4wFTk/blog-image/IP-teaching/IP-textbook-objects-2020.pdf&quot;&gt; Recommended IP Textbooks: Reading Plan and Student Presentation - Spring 2020 &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;two-new-textbooks-adopted-for-this-academic-years-ip-law-teaching&quot;&gt;Two new textbooks adopted for this academic year’s IP law teaching&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/icaruszhu/learning/master/image/blog-image/IP-teaching-book-cover/karapapa-IP%20-aw.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;IP-textbook&quot; style=&quot;zoom: 200%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/icaruszhu/learning/master/image/blog-image/IP-teaching-book-cover/50-IP-objects.jpg&quot; style=&quot;zoom:67%;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Chen Zhu</name></author><category term="teaching" /><summary type="html"> Recommended IP Textbooks: Reading Plan and Student Presentation - Spring 2020 </summary></entry><entry><title type="html">non-crypto-bitcoin</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/chen/bitcoin/2019/06/28/non-digital-bitcoin/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="non-crypto-bitcoin" /><published>2019-06-28T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2019-06-28T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/chen/bitcoin/2019/06/28/non-digital-bitcoin</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/chen/bitcoin/2019/06/28/non-digital-bitcoin/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;non-cryptographic-currency-in-the-making&quot;&gt;non-cryptographic currency in the making&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;尝试制作一种非加密比特币&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;是一种土法 量化宽松（Quantitative Easing）的方法&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;兼一种扰乱市场经济的行为;-)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/icaruszhu/learning/master/image/blog-image/bitcoin.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bitcoin&quot; style=&quot;zoom:67%;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="bitcoin" /><summary type="html">non-cryptographic currency in the making</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Copying Banksymus</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/chen/general/2016/01/01/bankymus/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Copying Banksymus" /><published>2016-01-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2016-01-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/chen/general/2016/01/01/bankymus</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/chen/general/2016/01/01/bankymus/">&lt;p&gt;Copying Banksymus by Chen&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="General" /><summary type="html">Copying Banksymus by Chen</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Law and Norms of Music Borrowing</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/chen/conference/2015/07/13/music-roundtable/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Law and Norms of Music Borrowing" /><published>2015-07-13T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2015-07-13T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/chen/conference/2015/07/13/music-roundtable</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/chen/conference/2015/07/13/music-roundtable/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;an-interdisciplinary-music-copyright-workshop--july-2015&quot;&gt;An Interdisciplinary Music Copyright Workshop  (July 2015)&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Co-organised by&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dr. Chen Wei Zhu (School of Law, University of Birmingham)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Prof. Paul Heald (College of Law, University of Illinois)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/icaruszhu/learning/master/image/blog-image/JC%20Bach%20op.%205%20sonata.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;JC Bach Op. 5 Sonata&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time&lt;/strong&gt;: 1.00-5.30pm, 13 July 2015&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Venue&lt;/strong&gt;: Birmingham Law School&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;session-i-music-borrowing-in-legal-and-historical-context&quot;&gt;Session I: Music borrowing in legal and historical context&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.30-1.50 	&lt;strong&gt;Paul Heald&lt;/strong&gt; (University of Illinois): The current development of music copyright law in the US&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.50-2.20 	&lt;strong&gt;Chen Wei Zhu&lt;/strong&gt; (University of Birmingham):  (Dis-)harmony and Harmonisation: Charting the European legal landscape of music copyright before and after ECJ’s Infopaq ruling&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(with further comments and elaboration from &lt;strong&gt;Lionel Bently&lt;/strong&gt;, University of Cambridge, &amp;amp; &lt;strong&gt;Luke McDonagh&lt;/strong&gt;, University of Cardiff)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.20-2.40 	&lt;strong&gt;Ann Allen-Van Russell&lt;/strong&gt; (Trinity Laban): Musical borrowing in the eighteenth-century: Efficiency, Education and Homage&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;2.40-3.00 	First Coffee/Tea Break&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;session-ii-reflecting-on-forensic-musicology--music-informatics&quot;&gt;Session II. Reflecting on forensic musicology &amp;amp; music informatics&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3.00-3.20 	&lt;strong&gt;Joe Bennett&lt;/strong&gt; (Boston Conservatoire) Reflecting on Forensic Musicology&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3.20-3.40 	Response from &lt;strong&gt;Guy Protheroe&lt;/strong&gt; (Conductor, English Chamber Choir)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3.40-4.00 	&lt;strong&gt;Daniel Wolff&lt;/strong&gt; (London City University) On music similarity from the perspective of music informatics&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4.00-4.10 	A mini-break&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;session-iii-musicians-and-performers-perspective&quot;&gt;Session III. Musicians and Performers’ Perspective&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4.10-4.30 	&lt;strong&gt;Ananay Aguilar&lt;/strong&gt; (University of Cambridge): ‘Law and norm of music performance: an overview’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4.30-4.50 	&lt;strong&gt;Izzie Barrett&lt;/strong&gt; (musician): A day in the life of an internationally active jazz musician and our precarious relationship with copyright&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4.50-5.30 	Open discussion &amp;amp; summary of critical issues identified in the roundtable&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;sponsorship&quot;&gt;Sponsorship&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Supported by a BRIDGE Collaboration Seed Fund&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(with special thanks to the Music Department, University of Birmingham and Prof. Lionel Bently, University of Cambridge for their kind advice)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;</content><author><name>Chen Zhu</name></author><category term="conference" /><summary type="html">An Interdisciplinary Music Copyright Workshop (July 2015)</summary></entry></feed>